Dreams of finding lost treasure almost came true recently.
A new machine called 'The Revealer' has been invented and it has been used to detect gold which has been buried in the ground.
The machine was used in a cave near the seashore where--it is said--pirates used to hide gold.
The pirates would often bury gold in the cave and then fail to collect it.
Armed with the new machine, a search party went into the cave hoping to find buried treasure.
The leader of the party was examining the soil near the entrance to the cave when the machine showed that there was gold under the ground.
Very excited, the party dug a hole two feet deep.
They finally found a small gold coin which was almost worthless.
The party then searched the whole cave thoroughly but did not find anything except an empty tin trunk.
In spite of this, many people are confident that 'The Revealer' may reveal something of value fairly soon.